{
    "id": "3a4f1e406578477fa6879b4cb958428f",
    "title": "Parts Of Speech Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "That was a brilliant performance. Here performance is a/an ……………………..",
            "description": "A noun is the name of a person, place, thing or idea. ",
            "answers": [
                "noun",
                "adjective",
                "verb"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "It has been a long time since I met him. Here since is a/an …………………….",
            "description": "A conjunction is a word used to connect two words, phrases or clauses. ",
            "answers": [
                "adjective",
                "preposition",
                "conjunction"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Why do you have such a belligerent attitude? Here do is a/an ………………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "noun",
                "verb",
                "adjective"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Seasickness is an unusual ailment among experienced sailors. Here among is a/an ………………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "conjunction",
                "preposition",
                "noun"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The accident was attributed to faulty brakes. Here attributed is a/an ………………………..",
            "description": "A verb is an action word.",
            "answers": [
                "verb",
                "adverb",
                "conjunction"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He is guilty of the awful crime of murder. Here murder is a/an …………………………",
            "description": "A noun is a word expressing an idea or act. ",
            "answers": [
                "verb",
                "noun",
                "adjective"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Germany, Italy and Japan formed an axis against the Allies in World War II. Here and is a/an …………………………….",
            "description": "A conjunction is a connecting word.",
            "answers": [
                "noun",
                "adverb",
                "conjunction"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "People who are too avid for success may miss some of the joys of life. Here too is a/an …………………………….",
            "description": "Too is an adverb. Here it modifies the adjective avid.",
            "answers": [
                "adjective",
                "adverb",
                "preposition"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The audience eagerly awaited the speaker’s arrival. Here eagerly is a/an ……………………………",
            "description": "Here the adverb eagerly modifies the verb awaited.",
            "answers": [
                "adjective",
                "adverb",
                "verb"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The natives were awed when they saw their first airplane. Here their is a/an …………………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "noun",
                "pronoun",
                "preposition"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The scandal was an awkward situation for the entire family. Here entire is a/an ……………………….",
            "description": "Here the adjective entire modifies the noun family.",
            "answers": [
                "adverb",
                "adjective",
                "noun"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We had cheap seats in the balcony of the theatre. Here had is a/an ………………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "verb",
                "adverb",
                "noun"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}